If the onboarding page does not start automatically, go to the bottom left to Applications, Accessories, Jibian Onboarding.
Once launched, click on “Configure your OpenPGP security key”.
I confirm.
Do you have a key? Yes.
Insert it.
Select Yes.
It is detected.
Continue.
Do you have the QR codes? No.
Create my OpenPGP identity.
I confirm.
Enter your birth name, given names, date of birth, and finally your country of birth.
Continue.
Here, enter your email address.
Then continue.
Check your information.
Continue.
Click on Print.
Print your QR codes.
Once this is done, click on Continue.
I confirm.
You can see that your key is detected.
Continue.
Do you have the QR codes? Yes.
Scan them.
Here you can see the first one, the second one, and the last one.
Save.
And that’s it, your key is created.